<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<addon id="skin.refocus" version="0.9.6-git" name="reFocus" provider-name="Jeroen">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="3.00"/>
		<import addon="script.artwork.downloader" version="1.0.7"/>
		<import addon="script.randomitems" version="3.0.7"/>
		<import addon="script.tv.show.next.aired" version="4.1.12"/>
		<import addon="script.watchlist" version="0.1.8"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" defaultthemename="Textures.xbt" effectslowdown="1.00" debugging="false">
		<res width="1280" height="720" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="720p" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary>reFocus by Jeroen</summary>
		<summary lang="nl">reFocus door Jeroen</summary>
		<summary lang="es">reFocus, hecho por Jeroen</summary>
		<summary lang="pl">reFocus autorstwa Jeroena</summary>
		<summary lang="de">reFocus, von Jeroen</summary>
		<description>reFocus is a reimaging of the original Focus skin released in 2008 and was created from the ground up. and although visually there are a lot of differences it shares the same philosophy as it's predecessor. Which is to provide a clean, minimalistic and smooth user experience, putting your media at the center of your experience.</description>
		<description lang="nl">reFocus is een complete herziening van de originele Focus skin welke werd uitgebracht in 2008. En ook al zijn er grote visuele verschillen, het heeft nog het zelfde uitgangspunt. En dat is het bieden van een strakke, minimalistische gebruikerservaring, waarbij jouw media in het middelpunt staat.</description>
		<description lang="es">reFocus es el rediseño del skin Focus, lanzado el 2008. Aunque la experiencia visual es bastante distinta, la filosofía es la misma que la del skin original: una interfaz limpia, sencilla y minimalística que aporte una gran visibilidad de los textos a una distancia considerable y poniendo los contenidos multimedia cómo principal objeto de la experiencia visual.</description>
		<description lang="pl">reFocus to całkowite przeobrażenie poprzedniej skóry Focus, wydanej w 2008 roku. Pomimo wielu róźnić w podejściu do prezentacji materiałów, nowa skóra oparta jest o tę samą filozofię co jej poprzedniczka, która zakłada lekkość, minimalizm i płynność, stawiając Twoje media w centrum doznań.</description>
		<description lang="de">reFocus ist ein komplettes redesign des Focus Skins, der 2008 veröffentlicht wurde. Und trotzdem dieser Skin sich optisch sehr vom Original unterscheidet, sind beide mit der selbe Philosophie erstellt worden: Eine glatte, minimalistische Oberfläche zu entwickeln, die deine Medien in den Mittelpunkt des Erlebnisses setzt.</description>
		<disclaimer>mouse usage not supported</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nl">muis bediening wordt niet ondersteund</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es"></disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pl"></disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="de"></disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>